<resources>
    <string name="app_name">ClintonBodyShop</string>
    <string name="title_activity_maps">Map</string>
    <string name="about_us">"Our repair experts are thoroughly trained in the use of our equipment and its exacting application in the repair process. Our technicians are PPG certified collision specialists and receive ongoing training from ICAR and ASE (industry certification programs that provide ongoing technical training in the collision repair business). In addition, the manufacturers of our high-tech frame, body repair, and paint systems keep our technicians up to date with new technology and use of their equipment and materials.\n\nOne Stop Shop\nWe are a one stop full service shop.We offer frame straightening, unibody alignment, minor to major refinish work including all-over paint jobs and custom paint.\n\nUse Quality Parts\nTo repair your car to the best of our ability utilizing the most highly respected brand of equipment and materials available to our industry.\n\nTrain Employees\nTo make training of everyone involved in the service process be an ongoing positive part of their job at Clinton Body Shop.\n\nRespect Customers\nTo treat you with the same respect we would expect at a business.\n\nMaintain Relationships\nTo maintain a positive relationship with the customer and the insurance company so that we can provide the level of quality in our repairs your car deserves and for which we are known.\n\nMinimize Downtime\nTo minimize the down time on your car by making repairs right the first time.  We know you don’t have time to have the same job done twice.\n\nHelp Our Community\nTo be good business citizens and help our community as much as possible."</string>
    <string name="faqs">"If my vehicle's frame is damaged, can it be saved and repaired?\n\nIn many cases, it is possible to repair a vehicle’s frame if it’s been damaged in a collision. We use Car-O-Liner frame-straightening equipment and premium-quality welders to repair unibody frames and sections. Whenever possible, we’ll bring your vehicle back into alignment, restoring the handling and ride that it had before its collision. On the other hand, if the frame is damaged to the point where it cannot be restored to a safe condition, we’ll be straightforward with you about that too.\n\nCan I get a rental car from Clinton Body Shop?\n\nYes, Clinton Body Shop has arrangements with several rental car agencies near our shop, and they provide pick-up and drop-off service for customers at our facility.\n\nCan you match my vehicles exact paint color?\n\nYes. Clinton Body Shop uses a state-of-the-art PPG paint mixing system that makes customized, highly exact colors and finishes. This system will match any color on any vehicle of any model, make, and year.\n\nIs there a warranty on Clinton Body Shop Repairs?\n\nYes, all Warranty on parts and materials are by the manufacturer of the part or material. All warranty on labor and workmanship for repairs performed by Clinton Body Shop, Inc. are for the duration of the ownership by the person for whom it was repaired..\nThis guarantee covers labor only and does not apply to parts, material or equipment which may be covered by a manufacturer’s warranty.\n\nHow will I know if my vehicle is done?\n\nAt Clinton Body Shop, we make it a point to keep you updated on the status of your vehicle. We contact you at every important step in the repair process, including the moment when your vehicle’s repairs are complete."</string>
</resources>
